const questions = [
    {
        question: "Who was the chief god in greek mythology?",
        a: "Apollo",
        b: "Poseidon",
        c: "Hades",
        d: "Zeus",
        correct: "d",
    },
    {
        question: "In what unusual way was Athena born?",
        a: "She was transformed from a wolf",
        b: "She sprang out of Zeus' head",
        c: "She was carved from marble",
        d: "She emerged from a giant clam",
        correct: "b",
    },
    {
        question: "What effect did Medusa's head have on people?",
        a: "It turned them to stone",
        b: "It gave them the ability to fly",
        c: "It killed them",
        d: "It made them fall in love",
        correct: "a",
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these mighty warriors was dipped in the River Styx as a baby, making him nearly invulnerable?",
        a: "Hercules",
        b: "Achilles",
        c: "Jason",
        d: "Odysseus",
        correct: "b",
    },
    {
        question: "What monstrous creature resides in the centre of the Labyrinth?",
        a: "Minotaur",
        b: "Sphinx",
        c: "Centaur",
        d: "Cerberus",
        correct: "a",
    },
    {
        question: "Who stared at his own reflection until he died?",
        a: "Sisyphus",
        b: "King Midas",
        c: "Apollo",
        d: "Narcissus",
        correct: "d",
    },
    {
        question: "Zeus assumed the form of what animal to seduce the Spartan queen Leda?",
        a: "swan",
        b: "ram",
        c: "dragon",
        d: "snake",
        correct: "a",
    },
    {
        question: "Best known as the god of the sea, Poseidon was also god of which of these?",
        a: "the sky",
        b: "fire",
        c: "earthquakes",
        d: "music",
        correct: "c",
    },
    {
        question: "How many gods lived on Mount Olympus?",
        a: "10",
        b: "400",
        c: "25",
        d: "12",
        correct: "d",
    },
    {
        question: "Who was the Greek goddess of the rainbow?",
        a: "Hera",
        b: "Iris",
        c: "Aphrodite",
        d: "Artemis",
        correct: "b",
    },
];